# **Ovarro Hanson**

160B Attingham Drive, Dudley, DY1 3HY

Phone (mobile): 07498167172 - <u>ovarrohanson18@yahoo.com</u>, <u>linkedin.com/in/ovarro-hanson</u>

## **Professional summary**

A dedicated and versatile professional with ten years of experience in combining management and customer service expertise. I have a proven record of reliability, problem-solving skills, and obtaining results to meet the requirements of local customers and international business partners.

I am currently seeking a job as a cloud system operator as I believe that my characteristics and pervious skills combined with my AWS training make me a great asset to the police force's cloud operations development team.

### Skill

- Time management
- Administration and management
- AWS-cloud computing concepts and core services
- · Linux, python, networking
- Critical thinking

# **Experience**

15/07/2020 09/2020

## AWS re/Start program

#### Cloud Ops engineer (trainee)

 Linux (CLI), Networking, Security, Introduction to programming and databases, Python, Cloud Computing concepts and core services. I am able to complete a number of tasks using Linux CLI such as: manage users and groups, Create and edit text files, Create, delete, copy, and move files and directories.

05/2013 to 11/2019

#### **Property Manager**

Bromfield's Property - Southfield, Saint Elizabeth, Jamaica

- Collect and deposit money into accounts, disburse funds from cash accounts to pay bills or invoices, keep records of collections and disbursements, and ensure that accounts are balanced.
- Meet with prospective tenants to show properties, explain terms of occupancy.
- Act as liaisons between tenants and owners.
- Investigate complaints, disturbances and violations and resolve problems following management rules and regulations.

• This role allowed me to build excellent communication and persuasive skills, along with improving my numerical reasoning.

03/2013 to 7/2018

### **General Manager**

Young Dreamers Research Center - Southfield, Saint Elizabeth, Jamaica

- Use computers for various applications, such as database management or word processing.
- Collect and deposit money into accounts, disburse funds from cash accounts to pay bills or invoices, keep records of collections and disbursements, and ensure that accounts are balanced.
- Operate office equipment, such as: copiers or phone systems, configuring router and arrange for repairs when equipment malfunctions.
- I learned how to take personal responsibility, demonstrated team work, adopted growth mindset and persistence.

09/2018 to 10/2019

#### **Private Hire Taxi**

Self Employed - Southfield, Saint Elizabeth, Jamaica

- Follow safety regulations and laws governing vehicle operation, and ensure that passengers follow safety regulations.
- Arrange to pick up particular customers or groups on a regular schedule.
- This job allowed me to better develop my customer service and time management.

08/2009 to 09/2010

#### **Senior Sales Assistant**

MEPCO Electrical - Junction, Saint Elizabeth, Jamaica

- Perform sales floor work, such as greeting or assisting customers, stocking shelves, or taking inventory.
- Plan store layouts or design displays.
- Opening and closing of the store, personal responsibility was a key skill I learned.
- Store maintenance
- Reporting to the owner

## **Education**

03/2020

#### Generation Uk and Ireland

Facilitator for the AWS re/start program

07/2009

Human Employment and Resource Training Trust/National Training Agency:

**Electrical Installation: level 2 (**the equivalent to **BTEC DIPLOMAS)** - Junction, Saint Elizabeth, Jamaica